这边，老大！
There, Milord!
我们有一个视觉上确认
We have avisual confirmation on
倒下的对象。
the fallen object.
这意味着你看到它。
Meaning that you see it.
好吧···
Well...
是的
Yes.
骑士阁下。
Be succinct, Sir Knight.
简洁是智慧的灵魂。
Brevity is the soul of wit.
是吗？
Yeah?
所以，告诉我——
So tell me --
what's the soul of
弱智者的灵魂是什么?
the half-wit?
砰砰
[ beeping ]
犰狳金刚!
ARMODRILLO:
Armodrillo!
哈！
Huh!
我敢打赌你的激光
I'm betting your lasers
伤害不到你自己的盔甲。
can't hurt your own armor.
外星人的技术是我们的，我们爱怎么用就怎么用!
That alien technology is ours
by right of salvage.
意思是“海底矿工”?
Meaning "Finders keepers" ?
啊！
Aah!
出来战斗,胆小鬼!
Come out and fight, coward!
(声音)
[ rumbling ]
BOTH:
啊！
[ grunting ]
哈！
Hah!
Nighty-Knights.
啊！
BOTH:
Ugh!
我想···
I was gonna.
你是在鬼混。
You were fooling around.
他是炫耀！
ARMODRILLO:
He was showing off.
专家说
Says the expert.
更多的麻烦。
More trouble.
好吧，各位
All right, folks.
我们可以从这里得到它。
We'll take it from here.
JT 和 Cash在的情况下。
JT and Cash are on the case.
如果你的孩子不介意
JT:
If you kids wouldn't mind
一边我们可以做我们的工作。
stepping aside so we can do our job.
你的工作？
Your job?
去年我听说,你的工作涉及到给家伙哭新生。
Last I heard, your job
involved giving wedgies to
去年我听说,你的工作涉及到给家伙哭新生。
crying Freshmen.
人们改变，莱文。
People change, Levin.
你做。
You did.
或者你还想杀了丁尼生吗?
Or do you still want to kill
Tennyson there?
不
No.
不是经常
Not usually.
嘿！
Hey!
你认为
JT, Cash,
what do you think
你在这里做什么？
you're doing here?
我们是水电工。
We're Plumbers.
他们是假货！
They're fakes.
他们当然是，但是
Sure they are, but
他们比我更好。
they're nicer than mine.
你从哪里来这儿？
Where'd you get those?
让我们别再讨论他了。
Let's not talk about it now.
我们是自信的。
We're on-camera.
这是另一件事。
That's another thing.
为什么我们自信？
Why are we on-camera?
Acerbus!
嗨，孩子们！
Hey, kids!
奥利弗·汤普森。
Oliver Thompson.
我记得你。
I remember you.
从视频游戏里
From the video game.
你工作时就只会长篇大论
You work for Will Harangue.
实际上我自由了
Actually I went freelance.
是的，之后他解雇我
Yeah, right after he fired me.
哈！
Hey!
离开那里！
Get away from there!
不要碰任何东西！
Don't touch anything!
你不知道他···
You don't know if it has...
【机器扭转的声音】
[ machine whirring ]
···一种自卫机器
...a self-defense mechanism
激活联系
activated by touch.
他做到了！
He did it!
【尖叫】
[ both screaming ]
[ grunting ]
[ beeping ]
旋风神龟！
TERRASPIN:
Terraspin!
[ grunts ]
JT, Cash,工作！
JT, Cash, work it.
关于你的一切
It’s all about you.
厄··
Terraspin, uh...
揍他！
hit him!
啊，还有小玟···
A-and Gwen...
用你的魔法！
use your Mañana!
知道了！
GWEN:
"Manna" !
[ grunting ]
完美！
Perfect.
就像我们的计划。
Just like we planned.
[ laughs ]
(⊙o⊙)哦！
Ow!
[ sighs ]
别担心，伙计们。
Don't worry, guys.
我很好。
I'm fine.
啊！
Ugh!
真好！
OLIVER:
Outstanding!
大家，这真的是非常好的表演！
Great show, everybody!
什么表演？
What show?
“得罪了！”
OLIVER:
" Alienated!"
我的新热网络直播,主演JT和Cash!
My new hot webcast, starring JT and Cash!
永远的骑士。
The Forever Knights took off.
好
Great.
好吧，你们给我说清楚！
Okay, bozos -- Talk fast.
好吧，我们有个博客。
Okay, we had this blog,
奥利弗说,他可以让我们
and Oliver said he could make us
成为有钱人或者名人
rich and famous if we just let a
摄制组跟随我们
camera crew follow us around.
We weren't trying to cause
我们不是故意惹麻烦，真的。
any trouble, really.
是Cash的主意！
It was Cash's idea!
实际上，
Actually, I just went along with
我就随他了
it, and I didn't mean --
[ both grunt ]
好的，说慢点。
Okay, talk slow.
等等，这是什么
Wait, is this about
这是你的博客对吗？
that blog of yours?
找一个地方说
The one where you say you're the
你背后的小班？
brains behind Ben?
一个博客，对吗？
A blog?
你为毛不告诉我？
Why didn't you tell me?
因为我不想
Because I didn't want
让你去追他们
you to go chasing after them the
下一次你变成暴虎。
next time you turned into Rath.
保护不会--
Rath would never --
好点。
Okay, good point.
除此之外，我不认为
Besides, I didn't think
有人注意到他
anyone was paying attention to it.
好吧，我是。
Well, I was.
因为我知道一个潜在的金矿
Because I know a potential gold
当我看到他
mine when I see it.
网络直播！
A live webcast!
JT and Cash在行动！
JT and Cash in action!
你是怎么知道这个外星传
How did you know about
撞的？
this alien ship crashing?
你们可能会与你的力量
You guys may be hotshots with
和天能人
your powers and magic
手表···
wristwatches...
但是我们的网络
But our network for spotting
识别传入的外星科技是首屈一指的。
incoming alien tech is second to none.
伙计们,我们需要看到一些
Guys, we need to see some
行动很快,或者我可能不得不
action soon, or I may have to
重新考虑这个主意。
rethink this whole idea.
[ rumbling ]
嘿！看！
Hey! Look!
我们得快点去看看！
Let's go check it out!
小班，事实是你拥有一切。
Ben, the truth is you've got it all.
超级大国，女孩，名声，女孩。
Superpower. Girls. Fame. Girls.
我们只是两个···
And we're just a couple of...
女孩吗？
Girls?
···无名之辈
...nobodies.
我们只是无名之辈而已···
We're just nobodies...
···想要成为某人的。
...trying to be somebodies.
加,你欠我们,小班
Plus -- You owe us, Tennyson.
在学校了你身边,嗯?
Who took your side at school, huh?
这是真的。
[ sighs ]
That's true.
整个是无名之辈,不容易承认。
And the whole thing
about being nobodies -- that
整个是无名之辈,不容易承认。
couldn't have been easy for them
to admit.
也许它不会伤害。
Maybe it wouldn't hurt.
有一段时间，好吗？
For a while, okay?
我们将会看看会发生什么。
We'll see how it goes.
算了吧。
Forget it.
别把我算在内。
Count me out.
我们会给你们百分之十的
We'll give you 10% of the
收入来源
revenue stream.
50.
30，加上一个签约奖金。
30, plus a signing bonus up front.
让我们施一些魔法。
Let's make some magic.
是的，我们不可能看起来不多
Yeah, we may not look like
但小班会不见
much, but Ben 10 would be lost
我们将丢失
without us.
都看镜头
We call all the shots.
我们的行动要经大脑想一想。
We're the brains behind the operation.
大脑，是吗
PSYPHON:
The brains, eh?
我应该知道。
I should have known.
永远的骑士是什么？
What were the Forever Knights after?
没有任何明确的承诺。
Nothing specific.
他们总是在寻找外星科技。
They're always looking for alien tech.
事实上,我听见他们说
Actually, I heard them say
他们会得到什么
they'd gotten what they needed
在起飞之前。
before they took off.
也许我们应该跟踪他们。等一等。
Maybe we should track them down. Hold on.
什么都没有
Nothing.
我可以做得更好，如果我有一个
I could do better if I had some
物品。
sort of personal item.
哇！嗷！
Whoa! Ow!
这是什么？
What's this?
一个外星机件
It’s a laser lance.
酷！
Cool!
我的武器！
My own weapon!
嘿！
Hey!
武器是你需要的
A weapon is the last
最后一件物品。
thing you need.
好吧。我得到了他。我们走吧。
Okay. I got him. Let's go.
好的。
Great.
哦,它是好的,
Uh, is it okay if we make a few
如果我们先停一下吗？
stops first?
是的，我们还有最后一个节目。
Yeah, we've still got a show to do.
实际上,它不是好的。
Actually, it's not okay.
我们——
We --
太棒了！
Great!
(引擎加速)
[ engines revving ]
所以是什么样子的?
So what's it like being you?
太棒了。
Awesome.
我知道他！
I knew it.
看 Cash，额
Look, Cash, o-on second thought,
也许你的主意不太好
maybe you coming isn't a good idea.
危险！
The danger --
我不想说什么，
I didn't want to say anything,
但是我需要钱
but I need the money
因为
this'll bring in.
我妈要动手术
My mom needs an operation.
啊，来吧
Aw, come on.
他说的是真话。
He's telling the truth.
我可以看到他的光环。
I can see it in his aura.
看见他的光环？
"See it in his aura" ?
You just made that up.
That's where we
blew up Vilgax's ship.
We had Ben and
the others keep
him occupied with
good, old fisticuffs.
Meantime, JT and I,
we, uh, um, we...
Uh, set the power
core to overload?
They blew up the --
I mean, yeah. Sure.
That's what happened.
Good thing you got
them to pick up
your slack, huh, Ben?
This is where Ben got
outmaneuvered
by three old
enemies,
or would have, if I
hadn't been
calling the shots.
I don't remember it
happening that way.
[ clears throat ]
But I could be wrong.
This is where the null
void gateway was.
Ben got stuck in
there for a while.
Good thing I stuck a tracking
device on him or he'd still be
trapped in there.
Okay! Rath time!
You promised.
Fine, but let's stop
goofing around and go
get that Forever Knight.
BEN:
Are you sure this is the place?
GWEN:
Yep. Top floor.
It’s a trap. Has to be.
Or maybe the guy we're
chasing just went home.
I mean, are they
Forever Knights 24/7?
Why don't you just go
upstairs and
knock on his door?
Yes?
[ brushing teeth ]
OLIVER:
Oh, so you figured to get a
drop on the enemy coming
around this way?
Yup.
That's me --
Always using my head.
[ metal clangs ]
Ow!
Cut.
Maybe we can
save it in editing.
Look, I'm just a grunt, okay?
I'm off-duty.
Give me a break.
My friend over there
is about to turn
into something
that hasn't eaten
a bad guy all day.
[ growls ]
All right! All right!
The escape pod
was one of two
that fell to Earth recently.
We determined
they were fired
off by a space-going weapons
smuggler who
was about to get
boarded,
and he didn't want to
be caught with them.
Please don't eat me!
What did you take from
the one we found?
An energy source,
like a battery.
Let me guess --
it powers whatever you
found in the other ship.
It could.
And that would be?
A power decoupler.
BEN:
What's a power decoupler?
KEVIN:
It’s a big gun that
drains the energy out of
anything, stores it, and
converts it into
other kinds of energy.
It’s pretty nasty.
We have to stay on our toes,
since our source said the
Knights' hideout is in this
construction site.
The Forever King sends word
of his growing impatience.
It’s powering up now, Sire.
Soon --
Hi, we're the good guys.
[ growls ]
Wait!
We need to tell
you what to do!
Everybody okay?
No thanks to you two.
He did it.
I don't care!
I can't believe I'm saying this,
but keep your money!
Show's over!
Kevin, calm down.
They were just trying to help.
We don't need their help!
They're nothing
but trouble!
PSYPHON:
At last -- a chance
to destroy the
puppet masters
behind Ben Tennyson.
Yep.
Trouble.
You're Vilgax's flunky.
Psyphon.
PSYPHON:
Impressive that you remember,
considering what I now
realize is your
limited brain power.
Meet my REDS --
Robotic Extermination Devices.
So, you were the true
masterminds behind my master
Vilgax's defeat.
You watched our
webcast in outer space?
PSYPHON:
Oh, yes.
I find all of your primitive
computer networking endeavors
intriguing.
Okay, well, now you know.
So you know not
to mess with us.
Right?
PSYPHON:
Actually, I will
destroy you completely.
[ both whimpering ]
We're not gonna
let you do that.
PSYPHON:
This is none of your concern.
I'm kind of leaning
towards what he's saying.
Ow!
And now I'm
leaning toward you.
Guys, it's no big deal.
SPIDERMONKEY:
Spidermonkey!
It’s just some stupid robots.
Psyphon's no threat.
Vilgax was the one with the --
PSYPHON:
With Vilgax gone, it
seemed a waste
to leave all that
power untapped.
This is no cheesy
re-creation, fans.
JT and Cash
will actually show
how they overcame
the power of Vilgax!
BOTH:
Aaaaaaaah!
Okay.
Interesting strategy.
[ both breathing heavily ]
Say goodbye, boys.
BOTH:
Oh!
PSYPHON:
[ groans ]
Uh-oh.
Ugh!
You think to defeat me?
You're in for a shock.
Me too?
Aaaaaaah!
OLIVER:
Brilliant strategy, guys!
It was nothing.
SPIDERMONKEY:
Aaaah!
Aah!
Ugh!
Kevin, get up!
We're still in trouble!
Let me sleep.
We're always in trouble.
SPIDERMONKEY:
[ screeches ]
Whoa!
[ grunts ]
Aw, come on.
Okay, guys.
What's the plan?
The plan is that I
destroy them
for what they did
to Vilgax.
We didn't do anything to Vilgax.
We made it all up!
We're total losers!
We never helped
Ben Tennyson at all!
We had to beg
them to do this
show with us!
I even told
Gwen that we
needed the money
for my mother's operation!
I didn't tell her it
was for a nose job!
But she really needs it.
You're not even
worth destroying.
ULTIMATE SPIDERMONKEY:
Ultimate Spidermonkey!
[ growls ]
It appears you are
the one I wish to
destroy after all.
Ugh!
Wait!
Cash, wait!
I-I have an idea!
Forget it.
You get to fire a weapon.
A big one.
I'm listening.
Wait.
I've got a better idea.
I still get to smash
them, though, right?
I love the smashing part.
[ growls ]
They're heading this way.
Get ready.
[ groans ]
PSYPHON:
Excellent.
Let the world
see the final
moments of
Ben Tennyson!
Aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaah!
Huh.
I still got it.
KEVIN:
Keep away from that!
It could go off!
It did go off.
We used it to save Ben.
We're heroes!
Sure you are,
Mr. Mom-needs-a-nose-job.
How did you...
already got over
200 tweets about it.
But we really did it this time!
ULTIMATE SPIDERMONKEY:
Guys, it's over.
No more taking
credit for my wins.
We're done!
Oliver, you got the whole
thing on camera, right?
Nope.
Camera lost all
its power right
when Ben there
zapped the bad guy.
We got nothing.
And thanks to your confession,
no one wants to watch you.
Even the internet
thinks you're a
waste of time.
Now, that's pathetic.
B-but he didn't
zap the bad guy.
We did.
The gun we shot
made the camera
lose power.
We're heroes.
We're heroes!
Give it a rest, boys.
表演结束。
Show's over.